(Wil:)And we're back.
(Penny:)Leonard, why are you making
such a big deal out of this?
(Penny:)So our roles have changed a bit
over the last couple years.
(Penny:)This is the way life is.
(Penny:)And I'm sure in time
they'll change again.
(Leonard:)Great, you're not only
more successful than me,
(Leonard:)now you're more mature.
(Penny:)Okay, look, would it
make you feel better
(Penny:)if I did something dumb like
sneak out of work one day
(Penny:)to go audition for
a Kevin Smith movie?
That would be great, thank you!
(Wil:)I'm just gonna jump
in here real quick.
(Wil:)Leonard, a moment ago,
(Wil:)you were dead set against Penny
resuming her acting career,
(Wil:)but now you're all for it.
(Wil:)Is it fair to say that
she played you like a violin?
(Leonard:)Yes, it is, Wil.
(Josh:)So, I have to ask,
(Josh:)was the robot sexy?
(chuckles)
It was actually
(Howard:)just a mechanical hand.
'Cause that's all
you need, right?
(Howard:)You are my brother.